<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
  <string name="title">Select for help with settings</string>
  <string name="mainbut">Main Settings</string>
  <string name="ftpbut">FTP Setup help</string>
  <string name="savebut">Save settings</string>
  <string name="about">About</string>
  <string name="stub">Stub text</string>
  <string name="nohelp">Help is not available for this selection</string>
  <string name="title_html"><![CDATA[
      For help on the different sections, Select the screen that you want information on
    ]]></string>
  <string name="main_info_html"><![CDATA[
        <big><title>The Main Screen Settings</title></big>
         <p> <strong><u>Vehicle ID </u></strong><br>
         This value is <strong>required</strong>, it is used by the program for creating file names.</p>
         <p> <strong><u>Block Number </u></strong><br>
         This is not required to run this version, it is used to identify routes or trips. 
        These values are used by the agency to determine time points</p>
        <p> <strong><u>Operator ID </u></strong><br>
        This is not required to run this version, it is for agency use.</p>
        <p> <strong><u>Start Button</u> </strong><br> This button starts or restarts 
        the logging. The values <strong>must</strong> be set in FTP setup for it to start. 
        If there is a problem a message will show above the row of buttons. </p>
        <p> <strong><u>Pause Button </u></strong><br> This button will stop the 
        logging but save all the settings for restarting</p>
        </p> <strong><u>Stop Button </u></strong><br> This button will stop the 
        logging and clear the settings on this screen</p>
        <p><b>Return to the previous screen by touching the Back button.</b> </p> 
    ]]></string>
  <string name="ftp_info_html"><![CDATA[
		<big><title><center>The Ftp Screen settings</center></title></big>
		<p> <strong><u>FTP Host </u></strong><br>
		This is the name of the FTP site </p>
		<p> <strong><u>FTP Site Log on Name </u></strong><br>
		This is the User name that is used to log onto the site.</p>
		<p> <strong><u>FTP Site Password </u></strong><br>
		This is the password that is used to log onto the site.</p>
		<p> <strong><u>Directory </u></strong><br>
		This is the path to the directory on the FTP site and the SD card that the data is written to.<br>
		Be sure the path exists on FTP site before writing to it.<br>
		If it does not exist the FTP write will fail with no error message<br>
		The path will be created on SD if needed.</p>
		<p><u>Port</u><br>
		This is the FTP port 21 is Default</p>
		<p><u>Minutes between updates</u><br>
		This sets how often the position is logged</p>
		<p><u>Seconds between GPS updates</u><br>
		This is how often the position is updated. Default is 30 seconds. The smaller the number the more 
		frequently the GPS and time will be updated. The updates MUST be more frequent than the logging. 
		This is to ballance between GPS acuracy and battery life. </p>
		<p><u>Save Button</u><br>
		Will save these values till they are changed or cleared</p>
		<p><u>Clear Button</u><br>
		Will remove all these settings.</p>
		<p><u>Cancel Button</u><br>
		Will just exit</p>												
		<p><b>Return to the previous screen by touching the Back button.</b> </p>
        ]]></string>
  <string name="SaveSettings_info_html"><![CDATA[
      	<big><title>The Save Settings and Logging Options screen</title></big>
      	<p>Select the settings that you want to be saved for the next time you want to start this program. 
      	A check in the check box indicates that the value will be saved</p>
		<p> <strong><u>The Logging Options section</u></strong><br>
		Choose all options needed</p>
		<p><u>Most Recent Only to FTP</u><br>
		This will upload a file to the FTP site with the most recent data. The file will have the 
		Vehicle ID for its name. It will replace the previous file</p>
		<p><u>Most Recent to FTP Log</u><br>
		This will add the most recent data to a log file on the FTP site. The .log file will be named 
		the vehicle ID plus the date. A new .log file will be started every day. </p>
		<p><u>Most Recent Only to SD</u><br>
		This will write a file to the SD card with the most recent data. The file will have the 
		Vehicle ID for its name. It will replace the previous file</p>
		<p><u>Most Recent to SD Log</u><br>
		This will add the most recent data to a log file on the SD card. The .log file will be named 
		the vehicle ID plus the date. A new .log file will be started every day. </p>
		<p><u>Save Button</u><br>
		Will save these choices and exit</p>
		<p><u>Cancel Button</u><br>
		Will not save, just exit</p>
		<p><b>Return to the previous screen by touching the Back button.</b> </p>
    ]]></string>
  <string name="About_info_html"><![CDATA[
		This app written by BusFixer
		<p> Version Beta</p>
		<p>The Data is written as CSV<br>
		readable time, Vehicle ID , Block ID , Operator ID , longitude , latitude , Unix time, accuracy</p>
		
		<p><b>Return to the previous screen by touching the Back button.</b> </p>
    ]]></string>
</resources>